{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20holds%20the%20record%20for%20the%20most%20career%20touchdown%20passes%20in%20the%20NFL%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Tom%20Brady",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Peyton%20Manning",
        "Brett%20Favre",
        "Drew%20Brees"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20NFL%20team%20has%20won%20the%20most%20Super%20Bowl%20championships%3F",
      "correct_answer": "New%20England%20Patriots",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Pittsburgh%20Steelers",
        "Dallas%20Cowboys",
        "San%20Francisco%2049ers"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20term%20for%20the%20NFL%20draft%20pick%20that%20is%20awarded%20to%20the%20team%20with%20the%20worst%20record%20in%20the%20league%3F",
      "correct_answer": "First%20Overall%20Pick",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Wild%20Card%20Pick",
        "Golden%20Ticket%20Pick",
        "Top%20Choice%20Pick"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20holds%20the%20record%20for%20the%20most%20rushing%20yards%20in%20a%20single%20NFL%20season%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Eric%20Dickerson",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Barry%20Sanders",
        "Adrian%20Peterson",
        "Emmitt%20Smith"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20term%20for%20the%20play%20in%20which%20the%20offensive%20team%20advances%20the%20ball%20downfield%20by%20throwing%20it%20to%20a%20receiver%20downfield%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Pass%20Play",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Run%20Play",
        "Screen%20Pass",
        "End%20Around"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20NFL%20team%20holds%20the%20record%20for%20the%20most%20consecutive%20Super%20Bowl%20appearances%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Buffalo%20Bills",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Dallas%20Cowboys",
        "New%20England%20Patriots",
        "Miami%20Dolphins"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20term%20for%20the%20penalty%20where%20the%20offensive%20team%20is%20moved%20back%20towards%20its%20own%20end%20zone%20due%20to%20violations%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Offensive%20Holding",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Pass%20Interference",
        "Delay%20of%20Game",
        "False%20Start"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20NFL%20team%20has%20played%20in%20the%20most%20Super%20Bowls%3F",
      "correct_answer": "New%20England%20Patriots",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Pittsburgh%20Steelers",
        "Dallas%20Cowboys",
        "San%20Francisco%2049ers"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20NFL's%20all-time%20leader%20in%20receiving%20yards%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Jerry%20Rice",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Randy%20Moss",
        "Terrell%20Owens",
        "Calvin%20Johnson"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20term%20for%20the%20defensive%20player%20who%20catches%20a%20pass%20thrown%20by%20the%20opposing%20quarterback%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Interception",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Fumble",
        "Sack",
        "Pick-Six"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
